Somebody on this app said, you know, Amanda, you act like you're beyond reproach and that's what makes it difficult to consume your content.
Let me tell you all, you are correct. I am beyond reproach by strangers on the Internet.
No, I don't owe a single one of you who I don't know who typically is behind a picture that not even a person who doesn't even have a real name who may be a bot or not.
I don't know. I don't owe any of you. And none of you owe anyone else the ability to be reproached.
I make my content. You agree with it or you don't. I don't care if you disagree with me. I don't care if you don't like it.
I thought about it. I've researched it and I post it. And the assumption that I'm saying it out of my neck or I'm just saying it cavalierly.
Is this a reflection of how maybe other people are making content or how you would make content?
But I don't make content that way. So, yes, you are correct. I am beyond reproach on this Internet.
The people who get to reproach me are people that I respect and that I trust and that I know.
Smart funny it!